<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Дополнения on dopos</title><link>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/</link><description>Recent content in Дополнения on dopos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ru</language><copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:08:56 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>App template</title><link>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/app-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/app-template/</guid><description>Repo: dcape-app-template
upstream_name application package for dcape.
Upstream Project: upstream_name Docker: template Requirements linux 64bit with git, make, sed installed docker with compose plugin dcape v3 VCS service like Gitea CI/CD service like Woodpecker CI Install Via CI/CD VCS: Fork or mirror this repo in your Git service CI/CD: Activate repo VCS: &amp;ldquo;Test delivery&amp;rdquo;, config sample will be saved to config service (enfist in dcape) Config: Edit config vars and remove .</description></item><item><title>Nginx sample app</title><link>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/nginx-sample/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/nginx-sample/</guid><description>Repo: dcape-app-nginx-sample
NGINX sample application package for dcape.
Docker image used nginx Features This project contains
reference versions of core files for all of dcape applications since dcape v2: Makefile .drone.yml dcape-compose.yml samples for some nginx features: log real user&amp;rsquo;s ip from traefik data send gzipped static files custom error pages Requirements linux 64bit (git, make, sed) docker dcape v2 Git service (github, gitea or gogs) Install By mouse (deploy with drone) Gitea: Fork or mirror this repo in your Git service Drone: Activate repo Gitea: &amp;ldquo;Test delivery&amp;rdquo;, config sample will be saved to enfist Enfist: Edit config and remove .</description></item><item><title>PG Backup</title><link>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/pg-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/pg-backup/</guid><description>Repo: dcape-app-pg-backup
Postgresql database backup application package for dcape v3.
Docker image used dcape v1: none (used running dcape_db container) dcape v2: internally built image with name stored in ${DCAPE_COMPOSE} drone var dcape v3: dcape-compose (cron uses running dcape_db container) Requirements linux 64bit (git, make, wget, gawk, openssl) docker dcape v3 Git service (github, gitea or gogs) Usage Fork this repo in your Git service Setup deploy hook Run &amp;ldquo;Test delivery&amp;rdquo; (config sample will be created in dcape) Edit and save config (enable deploy etc) Run &amp;ldquo;Test delivery&amp;rdquo; again (app will be installed and started on webhook host) See also: Deploy setup (in Russian)</description></item><item><title>Config CLI</title><link>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/config-cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/config-cli/</guid><description>Repo: dcape-config-cli
Command line interface for dcape config storage enfist.
Docker image used none (used connect to remote dcape config service) Requirements linux (git, make, curl, jq) Setup git clone https://github.com/dopos/dcape-config-cli.git make .env [write dcape attributes to .env] CIS access token доступен на сервере CIS после авторизации (для авторизации открыть ссылку &amp;ldquo;Config store&amp;rdquo; и обновить страницу)
Usage make ls - получить список конфигураций на сервере make cat TAG=name - получить из хранилища конфигурацию для тега name и вывести на STDOUT make get TAG=name - получить из хранилища конфигурацию для тега name и сохранить в файл name.</description></item><item><title>DNS Config</title><link>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/dns-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dopos.github.io/dcape/addons/dns-config/</guid><description>Repo: dcape-dns-config
Config for dcape based powerdns server
This project contains Makefile and sample sql zone definition for loading zones into PowerDNS server.
Requirements linux 64bit (git, make, wget, gawk, openssl) docker dcape Git service (github, gitea or gogs) Usage fork this project into your dcape gitea in gitea project settings setup hook for server where powerdns service running clone project locally from gitea add your zones .sql by example from domain.</description></item></channel></rss>